https://edflaborworks.com/edfinc/privacy-policy

Services Overview
Our Capabilites (PDF)
Services Overview
Our Capabilites (PDF)
PRIVACY POLICY
Respecting privacy is an important part of EDF’s commitment to our clients, respondents and the general public.
INTRODUCTIONThe materials (“Materials”) contained in this Web site (“Site”) are provided by EDF Inc. (EDF). By accessing this site or downloading any of the Materials contained in this Site, you agree to the terms and provisions as set forth in this legal notice. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions, do not use this Site or download the Materials.OWNERSHIPEDF authorizes you to view and download the Materials at this Site only for your personal, non-commercial use, provided that you retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original Materials on any copies of the Materials. You may not modify the Materials at this Site in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose. Any use of these Materials on any other Site or networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited. The Materials at this Site are protected by intellectual property laws and any unauthorized use of any Materials may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws.THIRD-PARTY COMPANIES AND PRODUCTSMention of third-party products, companies and Web sites on the EDF site is for informational purposes only and constitutes neither an endorsement nor a recommendation. EDF assumes no responsibility with regard to the selection, performance or use of these products or vendors. EDF provides this only as a convenience to our users. EDF has not tested any software found on these sites and makes no representations regarding the quality, safety, or suitability of any software found there. There are dangers inherent in the use of any software found on the Internet, and EDF assumes no responsibility with regard to the performance of use of these products. Make sure that you completely understand the risks before retrieving any software on the Internet. All third party products must be ordered directly from the vendor, and all licenses and warranties, if any, take place between you and the vendor.WARRANTIES AND DISCLAIMERSEDF intends for the information and data contained in the Site to be accurate and reliable. However, since the information and data have been compiled by EDF from a variety of sources, it is provided “AS IS.” EDF expressly disclaims all warranties and/or conditions, express or implied, as to any matter whatsoever relating to or referenced by the site, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties and/or conditions of merchantability or satisfactory quality and fitness for a particular purpose and non infringement, or arising from a course of dealing, usage, trade or practice. EDF shall not be liable for any technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, which this site may contain. In no event will EDF be liable to any party for any direct, special or other consequential damages for any use of this site, or any other website, including without limitation, any lost profits, business interruption, loss of programs or other data, even if EDF is advised of the possibility of such damages.INDEMNITYYou hereby expressly agree to indemnify, defend and hold EDF and all of its agents, employees, directors, licensors and licensees (collectively, “Indemnified Parties”) harmless from and against any and all liability and costs, including, without limitation, attorneys’ fees and costs, incurred by the Indemnified Parties in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of these Terms of Use, or any of the representations, warranties, disclaimers and covenants contained herein. EDF reserves the right, at its own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you and you shall not in any event settle any matter without the written consent of EDF.APPLICABLE LAWSThis Site is administered by EDF from its offices in Florida. EDF makes no representation that Materials at this Site are appropriate or available for use outside the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use or export or re-export the Materials at this Site or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable laws or regulations including without limitation U.S. export laws and regulations. If you choose to access this Site from outside the United States, you do so, on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. These terms and conditions will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Florida, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws.PRIVACY STATEMENTThis Privacy Statement applies only to this Site. EDF respects the privacy of users of this Site and believes that such information should be used responsibly and appropriately. In general, all users may visit this Site anonymously and without revealing any personal information. We may keep track of visitors’ internet protocol addresses, the browser used and other related data. We analyze this data for trends and statistics. We may also collect information automatically provided to us by your browser about the type of computer and operating system you are using. This privacy statement does not extend to anything that is beyond the control of EDF and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable policies, laws, rules or regulations.Any communication or material you transmit to EDF via this Site, via electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, comments, questions, etc., will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary. When placing a purchase order through this Site, EDF’s primary goal in collecting personal information is to facilitate the order processing and to enable us to contact you if a problem arises with your order. However, EDF shall be free to use any collected or communicated information on an unrestricted basis, including but not limited to reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, and posting. In addition, EDF will be free to utilize any idea, concept or technique contained in any communication you send to this Site for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing and marketing products using such information.
561-844-8886
We pride ourselves on integrity, experience, hardwork and take great care in providing a safe, functional and enjoyable work atmosphere. Call 561-844-8886 or contact us today for more information and project inquiries.
OUR CUSTOMERS
We are pleased to have had the opportunity to work with some of the greatest companies in the aerospace industry, including Pratt & Whitney, Sikorsky, NASA, USAF, and Lockheed Martin.
learn more
COMMUNITY OUTREACH
For over ten years, our engineers have worked alongside students to help accomplish the goal of educating students in advanced robotics. Visit 179swampthing.Org for more information.
learn more
QUICKLINKS
Gas Turbine Engine Test Stands & Equipment
Rocket Engine & Turbo Pump Test Stands
Test, Manufacturing, Assembly & Office Facilities
Control And Data Acquisition Systems
Engineering, Drafting And Technical Services
EDF Laborworks Project And Labor Software
© EDF Incorporated. All rights reserved. Sitemap | Privacy Policy
Twitter
Facebook-f
Linkedin-in
